Please give us a message from Fusa-kun, thank you all for your hard work over the past seven years.
I don't think I've ever seen a program where the staff showed so much love.
I don't know what it means, so can I see the caliber of the observation? You don't go to a show when you don't have a basic performance, do you?
But the staff said it was totally fine.
What time here? Like that.
I couldn't say no.
They'd just ask me to come in.
If it wasn't for Corona, you would have come more often.
You would have come more.
I was very reserved.
Even so...
I guess that's why I'm not sure what's going to happen in the future.
I don't know if it will be on terrestrial TV or on the Internet, but I'm sure I'll be in some variety shows.
At that time, I hope that you will remember the faces of the staff, me, and Mr. Orakio, and do it in the same way as you did in this show.
Seven years is quite a long time.
I hope you will do what you have learned in those seven years.
I will continue to support them.
I will continue to support them, and my family loves them too.
I will go to your concerts again.
I am sad to see them go, but I will continue to support them as always.
I will continue to support you as always.
Thank you very much!
Thank you, Mr. Muji!
I guess it's me then!
To everyone at Worsta
It's been 6 years since I first met and worked with you all
It's been almost 6 years since we first met and worked together.
For me, it's been 6 years, while the program has been running for 7 years.
But at the center of it all was this Worsta.
I rarely became a fan of people I worked with, but now I've become a fan of Worcester.
I'm sorry to see it come to an end, and I'm sure everyone in the worship group feels the same way, but I hope that you will accept this reality and take a step forward into the future, strong and strong. I hope you will accept this reality and take a step forward into the future with strength and determination.
Militeco.
You are a friendly and kind person.
But your kindness sometimes makes you seem reserved.
That's a good thing.
But I'd like to see a tough girl like you.
I'd like to see a tough girl like you.
Well, child.
I think you have a special sensitivity.
But if you can't control that sensitivity
If you can't control it, it won't become a weapon to fight in this world.
I hope that you will continue to hone your sensitivity and refine it, but at the same time, try your best to control it.
Luka, I think you've become cooler and cooler over the years, but I think you're a really loving person.
I'm a little worried that once the staff is over, we won't be able to see your cool and relaxed side that you show in Confessions of a Confessional Practitioner or in the horror world.
Please let us see not only the cool Ruka-chan, but also the cute, funny, and kind of casual Ruka-chan in all kinds of scenes.
I believe that only you, as the leader of this group, can produce the best group called "Worcester" by wrapping and cooking these three unique individuals.
I know you have to go through a lot of hardships to achieve this, but please don't give up and take three steps up from the current Worcester and make it a more powerful group.
I support you from the bottom of my heart.
I will do whatever I can do as long as Worcester continues, so please continue to support us. Thank you very much from Orakio on December 13, 2020.
I'm sorry, on behalf of all of us.
What do you guys think?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Stop it!
But should we burn it?
I don't know, burn it.
You shouldn't leave it to me.
It'll leave a bad taste in your mouth.
You said it well.
Thanks for getting into the groove.
He was saying good things.
Maybe we should burn it.
Everyone, you know, good things.
Everybody, look, they were cracking up.
Thank you very much
So, I've conveyed Fujita's thoughts and my thoughts.
But in the end, I would like each and every one of you to send a message to everyone who is watching the show.
I would like each one of you to send a message to everyone watching the show.
Me and Fujita...
What?
Manger.
We wrote them too.
You made it sound like this was a surprise.
Oh, no.
Let's go around.
This is a good time.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Can you read?
Yes, I can.
There.Hey, there.
Please don't make it too close up.
Now, let's start with the four of us.
Dear Mr. Arakiyo
In the big case, this program started in February 2016.
This program started in February 2016, and one year later, Urakkiyo-san joined us as a mc.
We are very happy to have met you through this program!
We are very happy to have met Urakkiyo through this program.
We didn't have much opportunity to work with comedians back then, and we were very nervous because we were not used to working with them.
I still remember how we talked among the members about how lucky we were that Mr. Arake was so kind to us and tried to get to know each one of us from the very first moment we met.
Now, Mr. Orakio is loved not only by us but also by all the worshipers.
It was here that we wanted the program to witness such moments, and it was also here that they always supported our future, our dreams, and our goals.
Once when the program was coming to an end, I was able to enjoy the words and the girls that Ms. Warakiyo gave to each and every one of us.
I remember the moment when the show was decided to come back as a surprise, and to be honest, I'm really sad that it has to be this way.
Since Mr. Arakio joined us as a mc, the sta-sta scene has become more fun and warm, and we are like a family.
I still love this place even after all these years, but I wish I could have enjoyed it more.
But we always gave our 100% so that there were no regrets that we should have had more fun.
And of course, as mc, you went beyond the show and enjoyed the live like a fan, and planned events for us before the free live.
Mr. Araki, who always supports us with so much love and enthusiasm, is so encouraging and
We are so happy to hear that.
I love everything about you, even the way you chew the name of the show no matter how long it lasts or how many years have passed, and I want you to be our mc for all the years! Thank you so much for the past 6 years!
From the worst
Thank you very much, thank you very much, thank you very much, thank you very much, thank you very much, thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
It's a job, isn't it?
Thank you for saying that.
It's all about the food, isn't it?
It really is.
But to be honest, when I first started.
I really didn't know anything about wassailby.
I worked with a lot of different people.
But I never became a fan.
But it's so strange that I became a fan too.
I think it's very strange that I became a fan.
But I'm so grateful to be working with Worcester.
I'm very grateful for this time that I'm working with Worcester.
I feel like I have one more thing to look forward to in my life.
I'm sure everyone in the worship group feels the same way.
That's how I feel.
I'm so grateful that everyone at the workship has accepted me.
I'm really happy that everyone has accepted me.
I'm really happy.
I look forward to working with you in the future.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Well, I've already had mine.
I guess Fujita and I will close first.
Then we'll leave the rest to the members.
Let's have each member give a message to the audience one by one.
I'd like to say a few words to everyone who's watching the show.
To all of you who have been watching the staff on this day of tomorrow
Thank you so much for the past seven years!
From a fan's point of view, it's kind of weird when a comedian MC's...
But everyone has been so kind to me.
They even called out to me at the live concerts.
I have a lot of friends from the worship group.
I usually meet them at the venue.
We became really good friends.
I really appreciate that.
It's going to be over soon.
But Worcester is going to continue from now on.
I'm looking forward to working with you all in the future.
I'll see you on the field.
I'll see you at the site.
So, I've been MC for about 6 years.
And Fujita too.
Thank you so much for coming, it was a lot of fun, and again, thank you all so much for watching.
I'm sure you'll all have a chance to see me next month, and I'm sure you'll have a chance to see us.
I hope you'll have a chance to see us at one of our live shows or events, and I'd be happy to see you again.
Thank you very much.
One by one.
One by one
I'm getting a little sad... when I put this in the big one, it's gonna be great.
It's so big.
I brought these little pinecones.
I've got some pretty pinecones.
They change color.
It's beautiful. It's amazing.Beautiful. Amazing.
Beautiful.
The colors are different.
I feel like crying just looking at the pinecones.
You know. I'm going to cry no matter what I say.
Mmm.
Excuse me. Um...
First of all, ladies and gentlemen.
Seven years it's been going on.
Thank you so much for loving this show that has lasted for seven years.
Even before our debut.
We were not used to variety shows, we were not used to being on a TV show, we didn't know what was right and what was left, but we've had so much fun and every month we've had such a great time.
We had such a great time every month with our favorite staff, our favorite members, our favorite MC, and our fans.
We had such a great time with our favorite staff, our favorite members, MCs and fans every month.
I'm sure I'll remember it for the rest of my life.
It's thanks to all of you that we were able to experience so many things.
I really love this show, which has given me a lot of experiences, and I'm sad that it's coming to an end.
I'm sad that it's going to end, but I'll be back again in the future.
I will continue to do my best with the warmth of this important place in Stasuta in my heart.
Thank you very much for 7 years. I will go next.
Let me go in.
It's so beautiful.
It's so beautiful!
There's pink.
It's so different.
It's so beautiful.
It's beautiful, beautiful, beautiful. It's so different. Pink?
There's pink, too.
It's so pretty.
Can we see it?
First of all, I would like to thank everyone who has been watching this show for the past seven years, and the staff members who I met at the end of this show, which I love and cherish so much.
Urakishiro and Fujita, and the time we shared together through this program.
It was very important to me.
It was a very important and unforgettable experience for me.
I don't know... I haven't really thought about it.
I haven't really thought about it, so I can't really put it into words.
I've never really thought about it, so I can't really express it in words, but I really love this place, and I look forward to it every month.
It was a really happy time for me.
I hope that when we grow up again as a group, we can do something together as the same members.
I hope we can do something together as a group when we grow up again as a group.
I would like to do my best from now on.
This program is really a big and important place for me.
Thank you very much for everyone who has been watching this program. I can't take the pink out of this show. So cute! Wow! Wow! I'm on fire!
It's on fire!
Burn, burn, burn!
It's so beautiful!
Fire, fire, fire!
Oh, my God.
This is...
This is it, this is it, this is it, this is it.
I really want to thank all of you who have come across and watched this show over the past seven years.
Thank you so much to everyone who's come across it and watched it.
Oh.
Let's see...
Since our debut, or rather, since we formed, rather early on
I've been doing this show on Nico Live for the past 7 years, once a month as a matter of course, and it's become a habit. I guess you could say that.
So...
Well, not at all.
I'm not crying like this.
I've been crying like this for the past seven years, for the past seven years, for the past seven years, so, um, not at all.
I don't feel like I'm really feeling it while I'm crying like this.
There have been a lot of good times, a lot of bad times.
There's a lot of black history, a lot of bad things, a lot of black history...
But
It's because I've gotten cooler and cooler over the years
I've become so much more
What can I say?
Emotionally
I've never been made to feel unstable
It's exciting.
I'm so happy to be here
I was so happy when I was laughing.
With so much love
We are making this program with all of you who support us
I have enjoyed this program
I am so happy that you enjoy this program
I am so happy to be able to bring you this program.
I will never forget the love I have received from you.
I will continue to do my best.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
That's the last of them.
Can you see it? I learned that it's better to put this in the back.
It's easier for the camera to see it if you put it in the back.
Can you see it? It's glowing a little blue.
It's glowing beautifully.
Okay, okay.
I didn't really hear what you guys were saying, so I'm sorry if I said the same thing.
First of all, thank you all so much for watching this show after almost 7 years of doing it.
With this staff that has been around for almost as many years as EWSTAR has been active.
This sta-star that has been around for almost as long as we have been active.
There have been so many changes in ourselves and the staff around us, but this sta-sta has always been the place where we have been able to go.
It was a place that never changed.
There were a lot of times when I felt uneasy and worried in other activities, but this staff has always remained the same, so I thought many times that I would be okay here.
I felt that many times.
When the show first started, there were a lot of things that made me think, "What am I really being forced to do, even though I just started high school?
I was scared, but...
But the staff and the crew love each other so much, and I soon realized that we've been together for such a long time.
There are so many people who came to like Worcester because of this show, and I love the time I spend talking with the people who watch the show about things like, "That was a fun project the other day.
I also loved the time we spent talking with the people who watch the show about how interesting this project was.
I loved the time we spent talking with the people who watch the show about how interesting this project was the other day.
I'm really grateful to this program, which has witnessed so many important milestones.
I'm really grateful for that.
I will always treasure it.
This program started out as a program to help us become the kind of people who can aim for the world.
This program started as a program for us to be able to aim for the world.
We will continue to do our best so that we can be the kind of people who can aim for the world.
I would like to continue to cherish this program, and I hope that we can be that kind of existence that everyone who watches us sometimes remembers and smiles.
I hope I can be that kind of person that everyone who watches the show remembers it from time to time and laughs.
I've really enjoyed every episode and I'm happy to have been a part of it.
Whenever I look for something I like
I can't see it in the reflection
I can't see it in the reflection, but I can reach it
It was so close by
Let's start the summer with a thought that flew up into the sky
It was BIRTHDAY!
Thank you very much! 구독과 좋아요를 눌러주세요